

Senior Blockchain Engineer specializing in blockchain development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycles for dynamic blockchain, cryptocurrency, NFTs, and Decentralized Exchange projects. Well-versed in programming languages such as Solidity, Rust, Smart Contract, Graph QL, React, Typescript. Strong background in project management, customer relations, and technical consultant.

Erdenebileg Badarch

Phone:

+976 99 88 9402

E-Mail:

willcomeo022@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/erdenebileg-badarch/

Location:

Darkhan, Mongolia

STRENGTHS

- Blockchain Development
- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design and Front-End
- Good Communication
- Full-Stack, Full-Time, Fast-Delivery

SKILLS

Blockchain: Cryptocurrency, Non-fungible

Token (NFT), Smart Contract, Solidity, Rust, Graph QL

Web: React, Typescript, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, NodeJs, NextJs

Languages

English – Conversational Mongolian - Native Russian – Beginner Chinese – Beginner

EXPERIENCE

05/2021-Present

CTO – GHA Foundation, Singapore

- Generate perfect infrastructure of Blockchain System, backend, and roadmap.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developers to manage large and complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as complex back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

05/2020-Present

Technical Manager – Blockchain NFT, DEFI Communities

- https://ghart.io/
- https://cryptochampion.game/
- https://quint.io/
- https://www.digibit.online/
- https://metasnacks.org/
- https://innatefervor.com/
- https://metagraphx.io/
- https://animeversetoken.com/
- https://zonoswap.com/
- https://keyswap.exchange/

05/2018-Present

Blockchain Top Rated Developer - Fiverr

• Fiverr Seller Profile: https://www.fiverr.com/mxpjb69vsdujici

EDUCATION

2012-2017

IT Management Master's degree - Mongolian University of Science and Technology, Mongolia, Graduated 2017